<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<data>
	<parenttype name="Popular Categories">
		<childtype name="Quick and Easy">There's no time! But is there ever? If you're feeling like you need something super quick and super easy, then you came to the right place. Let's get you eating, stat!</childtype>
		<childtype name="Instant Pot">Was there ever a more magical tool in the land?! Here are a bunch of our faves using our most beloved little kitchen helper: the Instant Pot. Soups, tacos, main dishes, and more!</childtype>
		<childtype name="Meal Prep">Meal prep gets big love from us because it's so great to not even have to THINK about what to cook every day. Spend a few hours getting everything prepped and then the rest of your week is made! Now your brain space can be filled with, well...all the other stuff.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Vegan">This is the place to go for all the plant-based goodness. These recipes are keeping it vegan but still super satisfying and super delicious. Let's eat some plants!</childtype>
		<childtype name="Vegetarian">Eating more plant-forward meals is not only great for your body but great for the planet too! Whether you're a long-time vegetarian looking for some new inspiration or someone just trying to add a few more veggie-friendly options to their menu, here's the place to find what you're looking for.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Sugar-Free">Everything from snacks to dinners, we have a bunch of super tasty and super manageable recipes if you're looking to reduce or cut out refined sugar in your eats.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Pasta">Ugh, of COURSE we would eat pasta for every single meal if we could. But let's be reasonable, maybe just 8 times per week? Just, like, how do you choose between fork twirly or perfectly chewy or positively smothered in all the best sauces? Oh pasta, we love you so.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Tacos">Isn't everything better when you put it in taco form?! We sure think so. Here are some fresh and delicious taco recipes.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Bowls">Best directions for any meal: pile it in a bowl and eat forever. It's easy, it's healthy, and makes dinner customizable to what everyone wants. We've got so many bowl recipes to love!</childtype>
		<childtype name="Soups">Soup is the beeeeest! Honestly, it's one of our favorite food groups. There is nothing quite like curling up with a steaming cozy bowl of soup slurped by the spoonful or devoured with crusty bread dips. Yes yes and yes.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Salads">Traditional lettuce-chomping salads but also noodley salads, mayo-based salads, grain salads...so many ways to salad! We promise these recipes will have you feeling full and happy.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Dinner">&quot;What's for dinner?&quot; Gah! That question! Whether it's coming from your own tired brain or a family full of hungry askers, let's help you get that question answered!</childtype>
		<childtype name="Most Popular">Wondering which recipes everyone else loves most? We get it! You want the tried-and-trues! The ride-or-dies! The absolute keep-it-in-the-weekly-rotation faves. Well, here they are. Some of our most popular, best of the best.</childtype>
	</parenttype>
	<parenttype name="Recipes by Meal Type">
		<childtype name="Breakfast">The most perfect fluffy pancakes, eggs on eggs on eggs, crunchy granolas and baked goods for days. Who doesn't love breakfast?!</childtype>
		<childtype name="Lunch">Whether you're planning to meal prep for the week or you're looking for an amazing sandwich or salad to chomp on at your desk, we've gone through our recipes and gathered a bunch for lunch!</childtype>
		<childtype name="Dinner">&quot;What's for dinner?&quot; Gah! That question! Whether it's coming from your own tired brain or a family full of hungry askers, let's help you get that question answered!</childtype>
		<childtype name="Appetizer">Friends, how great is eating before eating? IT IS SO GREAT. Here are some of our favorite crowd-pleasing appetizer recipes to get things going.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Snacks">To be clear, we can make almost anything a snack around here. Spare buffalo chicken taco? Couple forkfuls of cold noodle salad from the fridge? Who put this homemade oreo here? But ok, we also have a whole slew of more traditional type snackables for you to choose from.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Desserts">We're not eating dinner just to get to dessert and we're certainly not having dessert FOR dinner but, like, just in case...here are some ideas!</childtype>
		<childtype name="Drinks">Not just stuff on plates around here! We have a whole lineup of bevs for whatever drinkable need you're serving, whether it's just a nice way to start your morning or an afternoon pick-me-up or maybe something fun &amp; fancy for the patio. We've got you!</childtype>
	</parenttype>
	<parenttype name="Recipes by Course">
		<childtype name="Appetizer">Friends, how great is eating before eating? IT IS SO GREAT. Here are some of our favorite crowd-pleasing appetizer recipes to get things going.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Soups">Soup is the beeeeest! Honestly, it's one of our favorite food groups. There is nothing quite like curling up with a steaming cozy bowl of soup slurped by the spoonful or devoured with crusty bread dips. Yes yes and yes.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Salads">Traditional lettuce-chomping salads but also noodley salads, mayo-based salads, grain salads...so many ways to salad! We promise these recipes will have you feeling full and happy.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Sides">Honest question: are sides actually the best part of a meal? I think sides might be the best part of a meal. Green sides, carby sides, cheese-laden sides - these are my top picks to round out any dinner!</childtype>
		<childtype name="Desserts">We're not eating dinner just to get to dessert and we're certainly not having dessert FOR dinner but, like, just in case...here are some ideas!</childtype>
		<childtype name="Snacks">To be clear, we can make almost anything a snack around here. Spare buffalo chicken taco? Couple forkfuls of cold noodle salad from the fridge? Who put this homemade oreo here? But ok, we also have a whole slew of more traditional type snackables for you to choose from.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Baking">Sometimes we get a little crabby at the fussiness of baking but then also we remember the importance of a perfect chocolate chip cookie or an apple cake that makes you tear up a little or HELLO A NO-KNEAD BREAD?! So here we are, with bakes we love.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Sandwiches">Honestly, we love a sandwich any time of day, so we’ve got ideas for breakfast, lunch, dinner, or just sandwich o’clock here because you can never really go wrong with a bunch of delicious things between bread (or brioche, or bagels, or tortillas…we got you.)!</childtype>
		<childtype name="Main Dishes">Maybe you’ve got pre and post show all set, but you are still looking for the main event! Here are a bunch of recipes to be the star of any meal.</childtype>
	</parenttype>
	<parenttype name="Recipes by Diet">
		<childtype name="Dairy-Free">Breakfast, lunch, dinner, snacks, desserts, options for everything and still keeping it totally dairy-free! And if you're looking for something super creamy dreamy with none of the actual cream, yeah we've got that too.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Gluten-Free">There are so many amazing and satisfying GF recipes that aren't just a bunch of sad salads! Bowls, curries, hummus, and, yes, even delicious noodley things! Here is a great gluten-free list to get you going.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Healthy">Maybe you're switching up some eating habits, maybe you're coming off a week of all cookies all the time, maybe you just have a bunch of kale to use up. Whatever the reason, here's the place to search all the healthy things!</childtype>
		<childtype name="Sugar-Free">Everything from snacks to dinners, we have a bunch of super tasty and super manageable recipes if you're looking to reduce or cut out refined sugar in your eats.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Vegan">This is the place to go for all the plant-based goodness. These recipes are keeping it vegan but still super satisfying and super delicious. Let's eat some plants!</childtype>
		<childtype name="Vegetarian">Eating more plant-forward meals is not only great for your body but great for the planet too! Whether you're a long-time vegetarian looking for some new inspiration or someone just trying to add a few more veggie-friendly options to their menu, here's the place to find what you're looking for.</childtype>
	</parenttype>
	<parenttype name="Recipes by Season">
		<childtype name="Spring">We're peeking out of winter and into the warming days and our eyes and hearts are all bright and fresh and &quot;Oh my, the sun is here again!&quot; Here are some recipes to put a little spring in your step...and on your table.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Summer">Looking for just the right thing to make for a backyard grill party? Or maybe your CSA has been bountiful but your recipe ideas...well, less so. Here, let us help! Some of our favorite recipes to cook up and enjoy while covered in sunshine and summertime.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Fall">The cooler weather is rolling in and we're so ready for warm sweaters and spices and cozy. Here are all the things we love come fall time.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Winter">We're ready to fill up our houses with deep cozy smells and stand over steaming pots of slow stirs. The weather is cold, but our kitchens are warm and, okay, maybe there are some extra baked goods in there.</childtype>
	</parenttype>
	<parenttype name="Recipes by Method">
		<childtype name="Casserole">There's nothing quite like a casserole to cozy up a chilly day. You get to throw it all in a baking dish and then plop it on the table later, all bubbling and amazing, and feel like a total food boss while everyone scoops and devours. From breakfast options to full on near-fancy options, we've got a list of A+ casseroles to feed the people you love.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Instant Pot">Was there ever a more magical tool in the land?! Here are a bunch of our faves using our most beloved little kitchen helper: the Instant Pot. Soups, tacos, main dishes, and more!</childtype>
		<childtype name="Slow Cooker">There is nothing better than getting to the end of your day and remembering your dinner is already done and ready to eat. Thank you, slow cooker, for making dreams come true! Cozy soups and stews, rich pasta sauces, swoon-worthy taco meats, they're all here and ready to basically cook themselves so you don't have to.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Sheet Pan">Hi, doing dishes is the worst, yes? Like, what a terrible reward for making an amazing meal!! Well, that's why we love the whole sheet pan deal. Throw it all on a single pan and chuck that baby in the oven to do all the work for you, and then high five yourself later when there's minimal cleanup.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Stovetop">Maybe you don't feel like turning on the oven or maybe you're trying to get real fancy with your single-burner while camping. Whatever the reason, here is a collection of stovetop recipes for your consideration.</childtype>
	</parenttype>
	<parenttype name="Recipes by Ingredient">
		<childtype name="5 Ingredients">These are for those times when even thinking about the prep takes up too much brainspace. Each of these recipes is simple, straightforward, utterly delicious, and only 5 ingredients! No long grocery lists here, let’s get cooking.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Avocado">Is there anything this buttery, nutritious, delectable little green guy doesn't improve?! Full of healthy fats and creamy texture, it makes every single thing it's smushed on, chunked on, or mixed into a whole bunch more delicious.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Bacon">Baaaaaacoon! Is there anything better than hearing a recipe features our salty pal, bacon? Likely no. Bacon makes everything better! From crumbled on top of summery cobb salads to tucked between layers of melty cheese in a sandwich to being an absolute star in date and bacon bites, bacon can do it all! Thank you, bacon. Thank you.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Bell Pepper">Nutrient-rich and running the rainbow, bell peppers are a lovely little add-in to just about any dish. Sauté them, roast them, puree them, or just chomp on them raw. However you do it, they're a bright summery pop of color and yum in salads, noodle bowls, sheet pan dinners, curries, sauces...you know, all the things!</childtype>
		<childtype name="Berry">Whether it's the peak of summer and you've got piles of fresh ones or those bags of beauties are stacking up in your freezer, there are few things not made better by juicy little bursts of berry. Breakfast, dessert, an interesting colorful pop in salads. Get them super tart or sun-kissed sweet...just so many fun ways to play the berry game!</childtype>
		<childtype name="Broccoli">There's just not enough celebration in the world of these delicious little green trees. Roast them up for the *most* chef's kiss salad, toss around in a stir fry, or let them steam and swim in some delicious creamy soup. So yummy, so full of good-for-you nutrients.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Carrot">Is there anything this little orange friend can't do? From soups to desserts to roasty side dishes, salad adds and crunch-makers, we've got a whole BUNCH (see what we did there?) of carrot recipes for you to love.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Cauliflower">What CAN'T you do with cauliflower? We've riced it for stir frys, made it into meatballs, roasted it into taco meat, blended it in soup, rolled it into gnocchi, whipped it into unbelievably creamy sauces...we can't stop, won't stop with this amazing little veg.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Chocolate">Please do not be shy if you also consider chocolate to be a food group. We accept you. And we have oh-so many ways to fill up your dance card with this sweet, wonderful, life-giving treat.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Eggs">The great and mighty little egg! From breakfast bakes, to sandwiches, to the many, many things we love to just throw a perfectly fried or jammy gem on top of, here are our favorite ways to love an egg!</childtype>
		<childtype name="Fish and Seafood">Fresh, delicious and super nutritious. Tossed with pasta, filling up a delicious taco or topping a dynamite bowl, here are some yummy recipes featuring our friends from the sea!</childtype>
		<childtype name="Jalapeño">Oh my, okay! There is nothing quite like the fresh zip and crunch of a bright green jalapeño pepper. Whether you're trying to add a little heat to a homemade ranch or you're looking to add some spice and color on top of your tacos, chili, soup, rice bowls, fried chicken sandwiches...you get it. Jalapeños on everything always is the answer!</childtype>
		<childtype name="Kale">Our favorite hearty, mega-nutritious, vitamin-rich delicious bit of greenery. It'll hold up to soup, a heavily garlicked sauté, an oven roast for a little bit of crunch, or a boost to your morning smoothie. Whatever your heart desires, kale can probably do it (unless your heart wants it to turn into chocolate. Like, we haven't tried, but we wouldn't put it past it).</childtype>
		<childtype name="Legume">Legumes, fun to say and they're fun to eat! But also like super nutritious, a great vegetarian protein and easy to prepare in so many delicious ways! Here are some of our faves.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Lemon">It's hard to find a thing that these little sunshine squeezers don't make better. Whether it's brightening up a sauce, a fresh bit of zing over a salad, or being the absolute star in a dessert-meets-breakfast bread, lemons are where it's at. Grab that citrus and let's do this.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Lime">What a fresh squeezer of lime juice or zip of zest won't do for a recipe...HELLO, IT SINGS. A shower of fresh juice on a perfectly built taco, some zing in a deep rich curry sauce, or a little citrus burst to help every flavor shine. Here's your lime list, get to it!</childtype>
		<childtype name="Meat and Chicken">Here for a taco recipe? Looking for a stew? Maybe some delicious grillables or a best easy meatball recipe? We got you.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Mushroom">Okay, we know mushrooms can be a VERY CONTROVERSIAL food topic but listen, they are capable of so much more than being that tasteless unidentifiable squishy thing in whatever you ordered! They can be a great meat alternative and whether they are roasted, grilled, or sautéed in a swath of butter, there are so many ways to enjoy a mushroom. We promise we have some recipes to convince you.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Pasta">Ugh, of COURSE we would eat pasta for every single meal if we could. But let's be reasonable, maybe just 8 times per week? Just, like, how do you choose between fork twirly or perfectly chewy or positively smothered in all the best sauces? Oh pasta, we love you so.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Peanut Butter">We're not talking PB&amp;Js here (though there is definitely a time and place for classics). We're talking things like spicy peanut soups, savory-sweet tofu bowls drizzled with the BEST peanut sauce, and did we mention easy peasy peanut butter pie? Oh yes, there's pie. Let's hit that PB craving from every angle, shall we?</childtype>
		<childtype name="Pumpkin">Is it Fall? Are you looking for all things pumpkin? We are. Always. So here are all our favorite, cozy, quintessential pumpkin recipes!</childtype>
		<childtype name="Quinoa">Tiny little superfood, quinoa! Here are some tasty ideas using this nutritional powerhouse.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Rice">We are bowl-loving people around here, so rice is definitely a heavy hitter in our hearts. But not only is it a steamy, fluffy, delicious base for all the things, but we've also got some casserole, meatball, and even burger options too starring our little friend. Here are some of our loves for all things rice!</childtype>
		<childtype name="Salmon">These salmon recipes are loved by just about everyone! Salmon is hands down my favorite fish to make - it can be prepared just about any way, is endlessly flakey and buttery, incredibly easy and delicious, and full of all the good-for-you things too!</childtype>
		<childtype name="Spinach">Sometimes it's the star all sauteéd up with some garlic and butter, sometimes it's just a lovely little add-in for a boost of good-for-you and color. Whichever way you serve it — salads, sides, or smoothies — we love this little leafy green.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Sweet Potato">All hail the sweet potato! We're pretty gaga over these little guys. Packed with nutrition, a hint of sweetness, always adding that little special something to any savory dish. Here are a bunch of recipes featuring our beautiful bright orange friend.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Tofu">Not the weird flavorless soy cube you feel sad your vegetarian friends have to order, no! Tofu is an amazing versatile protein with so many different prep options to maximize flavor and texture. Bake it, marinate &amp; sauté it, whip it up into a vegan chocolate pie? Oh man yes, let's do this.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Tomato">There's really nothing like a ripe juicy tomato! Filling up your soups, swimming around pasta, fresh juicy bursts tossed in a salad, getting all roasty in the oven to add to a bowl or get scooped up by bread. Oooo yes, so much yum.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Zucchini">Maybe you came here for the almond butter chocolate chip zucchini bars, but you should definitely stay for the pastas, the zoodle bowls, and the lemon poppyseed muffins. If you've got zucchini to use, boy, do we have a plan for you!</childtype>
	</parenttype>
	<parenttype name="Recipes by Series">
		<childtype name="Feeding a Broken Heart">Sometimes all you can do is cook something. This is a collection of recipes dedicated to those finding their way back into the world, and the helpers who are getting them through the heaviness of it all. Cozy, comforting, nourishing...this is how we care for each other.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Holiday Series">Here is the spot for all your holiday planning! Or at least the food part, which…are there any other important planning parts? We’re very focused here. So bring on the cookies, the cinnamon rolls, the fancy dips. Say hello to side dishes and main dish recipes and okay, did we already mention the cinnamon rolls? Merry merry to you and yours, let’s get eating.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Plant-Powered January">Though we are not a vegan/vegetarian blog, we do have a strong love for recipes that not only provide some feel-good for our bodies, but also some feel-good for the planet. This is a collection of some of our favorite plant-based recipes that are just straight-up staples for us at this point. Yay plaaants!</childtype>
		<childtype name="SOS Series">What is life if not a series of “I’ve got this!” followed quickly by “Oh wait, nevermind, everything is haarrrrrrrd.” So it goes, so it goes. The SOS Series of recipes is for those days/nights when juggling kids and pets and jobs and laundry and life and...well, the &quot;ands&quot; just keep going...start to feel like a biiiiiit much. Those are the seasons when we let quick, easy dinners and shortcut ingredients be the delicious little life raft that saves us all.</childtype>
		<childtype name="The Soup Series">As an official offering to maybe our favorite season, soup season, here is our collection of delicious soup and soup-adjacent recipes that all have easy to find ingredients, big bold flavors, and lots of feel-good and good-for-you. Nothing like curling up around a cozy swirling steaming bowl of soup (or stew or chili)! And let's not forget those amazing dippers &amp; dunkables....lookin' at you, peppery torn croutons.</childtype>
		<childtype name="Sugar Free January">Sugar-Free January isn't a detox or a cleanse or some sort of very limiting crashy diet. It's just a challenge we do now and again to refocus and build some general awareness around our refined sugar consumption. It's flexible, it's about what makes you feel good, and you can truly make it your own. Here are super yummy recipes and tips that will help guide you down that path, should you choose it, while still keeping meals totally delicious and definitely something to look forward to.</childtype>
	</parenttype>
</data>
